

Contact

0981-708-0493

Email

Phone

Jaymedia143@gmail.com

Address

Cavite, Philippines

Education

2022

Bachelor of Science In Computer Science in Cavite State University -Rosario Campus

2016 - 2022

Junior and Senior High School In Tanza National Comprehensive High School

Skills

- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe Photoshop
- Time-management
- Calm under pressure
- Detail-oriented

JEREMY CHRISTIAN SOSA

VIDEO EDITOR & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

About Me

I am from Cavite, Philippines, and I have four years of experience with video editing using Adobe Premiere Pro and Adobe After Effects, as well as six years of experience with photo editing using Adobe Photoshop, which has helped my clients' businesses. Additionally, I have excellent attention to detail and strong problemsolving skills, allowing me to efficiently create high-quality visual content that accurately represents my clients' brands and effectively communicates their messages.

Experience

Freelancing 2022-present

-Video Editor & Graphic Designer

Since 2022, I've been a freelancer who helps my clients improve their videos in order to effectively showcase their business and attract more customers.

JPS 2021-2022

-Video Editor & Graphic Designer

My role is to edit a video that encourages OFWs from Korea to keep moving, working hard, and not giving up. And design a logo that represents their company that helps their business to grow.

Jek's Sweet Cake Delight 2019 - 2021

-Video Editor & Graphic Designer

My role in this cake small business was to design and edit videos for their business and to be able to post their advertisements and products, which helped them increase market sales in a short period of time. In addition, I design logos, cake toppers, and banners to promote their business on Facebook.